enence.com 2019-11-22

# Privacy - MUAMA Enence

PRIVACY POLICY

Dear valued customer,

At UAB “Ekomlita” (trading as MUAMA Enence, hereinafter – the “Company”, “We”, “Us”) we care about protection of your personal information and We strictly follow the requirements of applicable data protection laws protecting information about you at our Company. 

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully as it provides important information on how we collect, use and store information about you.  

  1. How should you read this Privacy Policy?

This policy will answer the most important questions about how we collect, use and store information about you. This information is important to you so please read this policy carefully. This policy may be amended from time to time. Please visit our website [https://enence.com](https://enence.com/) once in a while - you will find the latest version of this policy there.

  2. Who is responsible for protecting your information? 

We are: UAB “Ekomlita”, trading as MUAMA Enence or Enence;

Our identification number is: 305049890

Our address for correspondence related to this policy is: Gedimino g. 45-7, Kaunas, Lithuania

Our e-mail address: [support@enence.com](mailto:support@enence.com) 

Our telephone number is: +43 7200 22712

  3. Which information and why we collect about you?

Why do you collect information about me?

| 

Which information do you collect about me?

| 

Why are you legally allowed to collect my information?

| 

How long do you keep information about me?  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
  1.  For processing your purchase requests on our web shop, receiving payments and delivering purchased goods;

| 

First name, last name, delivery address, telephone number, email address, information about your paid purchase price and currency, your credit card brand, type, BIN number and credit card issuer country.

| 

We conclude and execute a contract with you (Art.  6 (1) (b) of the General Data Protection Regulation – GDPR)

| 

1 year after you make a purchase on our website  
  
  2. To ensure security of our website and  continuously improve it for you – where you visit our website

| 

IP address or other device address or ID, web browser and/or device type, hardware and software settings and configurations, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after visiting the Site, the pages you view on the Site, your actions on the Site, and the dates and times that you visit, access, or use the Services. When you use the Site on a mobile device, we may also collect the physical location of your device by, for example, using satellite, cell phone tower or wireless local area network signals.

| 

We have a legitimate interest (to ensure security of our website) (Art. 6 (1) (f) of the GDPR)

| 

1 month after you visit our website  
  
  3. To manage our accounts on social media - where you interact with us via our social media accounts 

| 

Name and surname, e-mail address, gender, country, picture, message, time and date the message was received, content of the message, message attachments, response to the message, time of response to the message, information about Company’s rating, comments on a post, post shares, information about post reactions.

| 

You agreed to that (Art. 6 (1) (a) of the GDPR)

| 

10 years  
  
  4. To handle queries, requests and complaints submitted by you – where you submit one

| 

Firs name, last name, e-mail address, country, telephone number, subject of your inquiry, date of your inquiry, content of your inquiry, attachments to your inquiry, reply to your inquiry

| 

You agreed to that (Art. 6 (1) (a) of the GDPR)

We have a legitimate interest to do that (to handle your queries) (Art. 6 (1) (f) of the GDPR)

| 

10 years from the moment your last inquiry was received    
  
  5. To protect our rights and interests for legal reasons 

| 

Information listed under Paragraph 3.1 above, documents and attachments sent to you, documents and attachments submitted by you, procedural documents, court rulings, resolutions, decisions

| 

We have a legitimate interest (to defend Company's rights in legal proceedings) (Art. 6 (1) (f) of the GDPR)

| 

10 years following the termination or your account with our website or, in case legal processes were initiated, following termination of such legal processes  
  
If the case arises - information about criminal offenses and convictions

| 

Data is necessary for the establishment, exercise or defense of legal claims (Art. 9 (2) (f) of the GDPR)  
  
  4. Which information you have to provide us with and why?

Please refer to the Answer to question 3 above - you have to provide Us with the information which We need in order to process the purchase requests that you submit on Our website. In case you do not provide us with this information, we will not be able to sell Our goods to you.

  5. Do we share information about you?

We share the information about you with the following entities only where necessary and permitted by applicable laws and for the reasons listed under the Answer 3 above:  

  * Paysafe Financial Services Ltd., a financial institution (payment processor) incorporated in England and Wales, company No. 04478861, financial institution No. 900015, registered office address Floor 27 25 Canada Square, London, England, telephone No. +4402036972413 (this company is used for processing payments that we receive from you for the purpose referred to under Par. 3.1 above);

  * Swedbank, AB, a financial institution (bank) incorporated in Lithuania, company No. 112029651, financial institution No. LB000298, registered office address Konstitucijos pr. 20A, LT-03502 Vilnius, Lithuania, telephone No. +370 5 2684444 (this company is a bank that the Company use for receiving payments from you via our payment processor for  the purpose referred to under Par. 3.1 above);

  * UAB Ismanioji logistika, a company (shipping agent) incorporated in Lithuania, company No. 304751937, registered office address Savanorių pr. 176, Vilnius LT-03154, Lithuania, telephone No. +370 672 88584 (this company is used as a fulfilment center which the Company use for distribution and delivery of the purchased goods as referred to Par. 3.1 above);

  * attorneys, attorney’s assistants, notaries, bailiffs, auditors, consultants, IT service providers, electronic communications service providers, insurance companies, archiving services and other subjects that provide services to the Company (data may be transferred for all of the purposes listed under Answer 3 above);

  * courts, law enforcement and other state institutions (data may be transferred for all of the purposes listed under Answer 3 above);

  6. How do we protect information about you transferred outside the European Economic Area?

In most cases, personal data are processed and transmitted in the territory of the European Union and the European Economic Area, but when necessary for the provision of certain services, the data may be transmitted and processed beyond those territories when the personal data protection level is maintained. 

  7. What can you ask us to do about your information?

GDPR and other laws provide you with certain rights, procedures for implementation of and exceptions to these rights. When allowed by law, you can:

  * Submit a request for confirmation that the Company is processing the data related to you. If the Company process the data related to you, request access to the data processed and related information;

  * Submit a request to correct inaccurate or incorrect information used or to supplement it when it is not complete;

  * Submit a request to delete the information we have about you if we use it illegally;

  * Submit a request to restrict the processing of your information – if you dispute the accuracy of the data or object to the processing of the data, if you do not accept that your data would be deleted which was illegally processed, or if you need the data to claim, execute or defend legal claims;

  * Object to collection, use and storage of your information at our Company – when we process data based on the Company's legal and / or third party interests;

  * Submit a request to transfer (receive) the data that you provided to us under the contract or giving the consent and which we process by automated means, generally using electronic form;

  * To withdraw any consents given to us regarding information used about you - when we use the data based on your consent;

  * To lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority and seek a judicial remedy.

  8. Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small text files that are stored by your browser on your device (e.g. computer, mobile phone, tablet) when you browse websites. Other technologies, including data we store on your web browser or device, identifiers associated with your device, and other software, are used for similar purposes. They are widely used in order to make websites work or work in a better, more efficient way. In this policy, we refer to all of these technologies as cookies.

Our website contains cookies as described in the table below. These cookies are essential for operation of the website so we will ask you to accept them in order to use our website: 

Cookie name

| 

Cookie purpose

| 

Cookie expiry  
  
---|---|---  
  
__cfduid

| 

This cookie is used to override any security restrictions based on the IP address the visitor is coming from. It does not contain any user identification information.

| 

1 year  
  
XSRF-TOKEN

| 

This cookie is written to help with site security in preventing Cross-Site Request Forgery attacks.        

| 

During the browsing session  
  
rpp

| 

This is used to hold information about your current visit with us. This cookie is essential to the functionality of the site.

| 

During the browsing session  
  
_vwo_uuid_v2

| 

This cookie ensures a visitor always sees the same version of a page and is used to measure the performance of different page versions.

| 

1 year  
  
enence_session

| 

This is used to hold information about your current visit with us. This cookie is essential to the functionality of the site.        

| 

During the browsing session  
  
_ga

| 

This cookie is used to identify unique visitors and is updated every time you visit pages

| 

2 years  
  
_gat

| 

This cookie is used by Google Analytics to limit the frequency of queries

| 

During the browsing session  
  
_gid

| 

This cookie is used to distinguish users

| 

24 hours  
  
Our website may also contain non-essential cookies as described in the table below. We recommend allowing these cookies to be active as they help to provide you with better suited content:

System

| 

Tag/Additions

| 

Purpose

| 

Cookie expiry  
  
---|---|---|---  
  
AdWords

| 

Conversion tracking

| 

For conversion tracking and marketing purposes

| 

1 month  
  
Facebook

| 

Retargeting pixel

| 

For marketing purposes

| 

3 months  
  
Facebook

| 

Conversion tracking

| 

For conversion tracking and marketing optimisation purposes

| 

3 months  
  
Google Tag Manager

| 

Conversion tracking 

| 

For measuring the effectiveness of advertisements 

| 

2 years  
  
9\. How can you manage cookies?

You can configure your browser to decline some or all cookies or to ask for your permission before accepting them. Please note that by deleting cookies or disabling future cookies you may be unable to access certain areas or features of our website. For information on how to adjust or change your browser settings, visit [www.aboutcookies.org](https://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.aboutcookies.org&sa=D&ust=1559641158079000) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](fhttps://www.google.com/url?q=http://www.allaboutcookies.org&sa=D&ust=1559641158079000).

For the information on, policy and control options for the third party cookies, please read cookie policies of such third parties.

Last Edited on 2019-06-04
